Kettle and Idol
Wook-chan at your service
Yes, ma'am.
Name Wook-chan
Yes, sir.
This is an important element, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
He's a one-year-old round cheese and poodle mix.
Oh, he just posted a picture of himself.
He's cute.
He's a boy.
A boy.
He's very energetic.
One year old?
One year old.
What kind of boy dog is Wook?
He's very energetic and loves people.
Uh-huh.
He's afraid of dogs.
Oh, really?
He's so scared he runs away.
When you go for a walk...
I'm sure he meets other dogs.
If they come suddenly, he runs away.
When we go to the dog run, he's really good at playing by himself.
I usually like to see dogs getting along with each other.
But he's always running around by himself.
I see.
He's very energetic.
Heh...
What do you think of Mr. Nakayama?
I wonder...
What do they think of me?
My brother is closest to my brother.
Then my mother.
Then my father, and I'm the youngest.
When you see a family of dogs...
Little brothers and sisters tend to be looked down upon.
I think I'm looked down upon.
When do you feel that?
When I put my face close to his and he kisses me.
And then, just when I think he's doing it...
Then she turns her head away.
I thought, "I'll do it just in case.
He does it just in case.
But even if he looks at me like that, he's still cute.
He's cute.
Just looking at me is cute.
When I came home, he was jumping all over the place.
Once he's in the cage, he jumps all the time.
He jumps all the time.
See?
I've seen him for a while.
You've been taking him a lot of places, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
Like during Golden Week this year.
The day after the concert.
On my days off, I go to the dog run.
or go to cafes where dogs are allowed.
We spent our time together.
What is Wook-chan like for you, Mr. Nagayama?
He's my little brother who really blows away my fatigue.
A little brother.
Yes, a big sister.
When I see a dog walking around.
Everything looks like Wook.
All dogs look like Wook.
Dogs?
If there's a dog walking, it's Wook.
Wook.
I'm not one of the many people who see dogs.
Have you ever thought that someone's dog is your dog?
You've never thought that?
I've never seen it.
I think "Wuk".
When I see a dog, I want to go home.
Like I want to see my dog.
But it's not like that.
Everything looks like my dog.
I don't know what's going on with that.
I'd like to ask someone who knows more about it.
So, that's how it is.
The second element that makes Mr. Nagayama...
It was the doggie case.
Thank you very much.
It's the first time I feel like I'm having a sister.
Yes, yes, yes
We sent it to you courtesy of organic products
Thank you very much.